

Moayad Myro

🖟 www.almyser.com

C +31 633 452 812

Background:

Full Stack Developer & Financial System Expert with more than 12 years experience in designing, developing and implanting a range of financial software and web based applications. Throughout my career I was able to provide organizations as well as entrepreneurs with custom-based programming including cloud and ERP systems.

I am a professional IT developer with a pro-active approach towards result oriented and customer focus.

I seek an opportunity to utilize my IT strengths along with my knowledge and background in finance to champion programs that add value to business deliverables.

Work Experience:

Freelance 2018 - Recent

Provide IT programming services for several clients. includes:

- software health check and updates.
- online marketing (google adwords, facebook, snapchat...).
- website and graphic design C# ASP.net or static (html,css,javascript) dependant on client needs.
- Services space email API's & hosting.

 Custom-base software development WPF or Windows Form c# entity framework SQL ,oracle databases sometimes ERD,UML. (full list below)

Experience History:

- 1. development of business modules administration, logistics and financials 10 years ago Created my own Accounting Software {Almyser 2012} multi language [ar-en] ,support all financial sheets and vat with encryption QR codes ,barcode generator reader inventory sales, parches, accountant chart ,finance list with reporting and search and most other accountant concepts.
- 2. I create learning game for android (2014) using game engines JavaScript java.
- 3. Marketed and sold my programs for several clients in Egypt, Syria, Bahrain, Oman, and Saudi Arabia.
- 4. Working on Updates for all of them on customers need.

AFAQ A | KSA Alriadh 2019 - 2016

Led a team of seven IT professionals to deliver ERP systems specialized in managing financial portfolio for several clients. Achieving this was through using most recent technologies such data entity framework to manage databases and link to frontend software. All programs were integrated using Application Programming interface.

- Create and design database ERD, UML, WFD SQL Server.
- Create and design several websites integrated with our database C#.

- Create and design android app integrated with our database java android studio and JavaScript with Web view plug-in.
- Create and design software Windows form c# EF integrated with our database.

Baytalejtiaz | KSA Alriadh 2016 - 2014

Consulting provider and Full-stack developer Custom-web, Software and apps based on customer needs many technologies and programming language was used such as:

I provide Mobile apps development & Publishing using : (Jquerymobile ,Phonegap [Webview] - Java Andriod Studio , Swift 3 Xcode [Native]) -Developer Console.

Also Customized Web application and Software's: (C#, 3rd part controls(Devexpress – Wix toolset – ComponentOne), Consulting. UI technology: (WPF, Windows form, MVC, ASP.net).

And Online Marketing: Google (Adword - Admob) - Apple - Facebook-Snap Ads.

Freelance 2014 – 2016 (Part-time)

Developed several programs for clients such as:

- University of Imam Saud; a web based application for talent analysis and statistics.
- Al Nahdi Pharmacy Chain; a program to monitor and retrieve clients debts and financial impact.

- Ministry of Interior; a custom based logistics and financial tracking software to manage export and import of radioactive chemicals and materials.
- Other small and medium projects includes web sites, applications and custom based programming.

Saudi Company for Construction Development 2013

(Hardware & Software) managing and maintenance the network hardware and software configuration .

Syria Yaafour Bassadors Street 2009-2011

IT Manager: In charge of a range of IT services including hardware and software repairs internal networks, server installation repair and follow up. Handled accounting software maintenance and reporting.

Other: University of Technology, Malaysia 2018-2019

Artificial intelligence and data science. In coordination with students and a professors in Malaysia, I worked on a masters project, developing a comprehensive IT program to analyze data with the aim of helping and evaluating social life of people suffering from mental illness. Several techniques were used, including: negative list ,SVM ,NL ,ML ,Classification. The program was successful and won the approval of the University.

Other: Saudi Arabia for children's amusement parks

Used software for gate control and customize it for the needs of the Amusement Parks to link electronic gates that work on NFC tags technology. The outcome was integrated and streamlined system allowing for fully automated game monitoring and financial calculation with an alert and security modules supporting the program. Data is fully integrated and linked to administration, parents and the accounts.

- Study and research about automatic doors how they work.
- Install windows server, connect the server with doors.
- Setup API in the server to connect with bank services.
- Programming and install NFC reader NFC SDK and connect them with sensors in the automatic doors open create a sounds send request to API in the server to check current balance and transfer data.

Qualifications:

2005-2009 Finance and Accounting Damascus University–
Syria

Diploma Technical in Providence and Business (Accountant)

2009-2012 Syrian University Bachelor In Information Technology

SKILLS:

- 1. Full stack developer Web base Rotterdam 04/2022 Front-Back end certified html, CSS, react JS ,Word press etc.
- 2. Office certified 1/4/2009 International Computer Driving License ICDL.
- 3. certified 1/10/2009Oracle11g (PL/SQL) training course.

- 4. certified MCSE 10/12/2009 : Planning Implementing and Maintaining Microsoft Windows server 2003-2008 Active Directory Infrastructure .
- 5. Accountant programs with certified 3/5/2011 : Al Ameen, AL Rashed , AL Adaare .
- 6. 2012 certified CPU ICORE Family 3G from Intel company In Kingdom Saudi Arabia /Exit 9 Extra Garnada.

Language: I speak Arabic, English, Spanish, Dutch

Knowledge and experience IT Technologies and programs
accounting knowledge and skills
Software programming C#
Web Development (ASP –MVC C#)
Application (Javascript – Swift – Java)
Game programming (core/tools/gameplay) in C#/ javascript
Cloud development in Azure
Little background bout A++ / PLC / Maintenance
Networking
Google/ Apple Developer Console
Marketing CEO Google ,Social Media APIs / Ads
Unity3D / Cocos2d / Constructor 2-3 2d Games
DBMS Oracle / SQL (PL-SQL-Management)
UML/ERD/WDF
Photoshop / Video Maker – Editing
Linux / Cyber Security /Social-Reverse engineering /packaging